get comprehensive critical illness
coverage that gives you 100 of what you
need when you need it
FWD critical illness plus provides you
with multiple payouts you'll be covered
for a second claim via the auto reload
benefit get 100 payout for early stages
of cancer heart attack and stroke and
still be covered at 100 of your sum
insured for 37 late stage critical
illnesses
you can also choose to enhance your
coverage with our ICU benefit add-on
that protects you with 100 payout
regardless of injuries or illnesses
including any unknown and emerging
illnesses
with FWD it is easy to buy and just as
easy to claim in the event of a claim
rest assured that your dedicated claims
associate will be here to guide you FWD
critical illness Plus Insurance from
just 100 a month with no medical checkup
required buy online now
[Music]